<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="XML Quick...">
   <intro href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/html/quickfunctions/quickfunctions.html">
      <description>
         Welcome to the <b>XML Quick Functions</b>  tutorial of the <b>Eclipse XML Security Tools</b>.<br/>
This tutorial will show you the general usage of the different quick functions. You will enter the necessary information on the preference pages to activate these functions and to get an overview of all possibilities. To start this tutorial click the <b>Click to Begin</b> link below.<br/>
By the way, this tutorial only introduces you to some of the many possibilities of the <b>XML Quick Functions</b>. You can find more information in the online help of the XML Security Tools by simply clicking on any help icon in this cheat sheet.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Preferences" dialog="true" skip="true" href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/html/preferences/general.html">
      <description>
         The first required step is to provide the necessary information in your workspace preferences. You have to enter all information normally provided in the respective wizard (except passwords).<br/>
You can skip this item if you already entered this information.
      </description>
      <action class="org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.ui.cheatsheets.OpenPreferences" pluginId="org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.ui" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Project and XML document" dialog="true" skip="true" href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/tasks/tasks-42.htm">
      <description>
         Now it is time to create a new project (all your XML documents must be part of a project to work properly with the <b>XML Security Tools</b>). It doesn&apos;t matter what type of project. After that you create a new XML document with arbitrary elements, attributes and any content.<br/>
It is advisable to start with a small XML document and to extend it step by step. You can create a sample project and a sample XML document automatically by clicking on the <b>Click to Perform</b> link below. You can skip this step (<b>Click to Skip</b> link) if you already have a project and a contained XML document.
      </description>
      <action class="org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.ui.cheatsheets.CreateSampleProject" pluginId="org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.ui" confirm="false">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Quick functions" dialog="true" skip="false" href="/org.eclipse.wst.xml.security.doc/html/quickfunctions/quickfunctions.html">
      <description>
         You are now ready to use a quick function: right click in the (XML) editor, select <b>XML Security</b> in the context menu and click on any of the quick functions provided (<b>Quick [Signature | Verification | Encryption | Decryption]</b>).<br/>
All following steps depend on the selected quick function. Some functions ask you to enter sensitive data (like passwords in <b>Quick Signature</b>); some don&apos;t and show the result directly (like <b>Quick Verification</b>).<br/>
If required preferences are missing a dialog will inform you. You can then provide the missing information directly in the dialog by clicking on the link or skip the action.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
