<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<contexts>
   <context id="wizard_signature">
      <description>Creates a new XML Signature with the help of a wizard.</description>
      <topic href="tasks/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
   </context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_resource">
		<description>Select a &lt;b&gt;resource&lt;/b&gt; to sign (the complete document or a fragment of it), the &lt;b&gt;signature type&lt;/b&gt; (enveloping, enveloped or detached) and a &lt;b&gt;key option&lt;/b&gt; (create a new one or use an existing one). The &lt;b&gt;Basic Security Profile&lt;/b&gt; option increases interoperability of Web Service Security.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="tasks/sign_page_resource.html" label="Resource and Signature Type"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_open_key">
		<description>Provide all required information for the &lt;b&gt;key to use&lt;/b&gt; in the current signing process.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="tasks/sign_page_open_key.html" label="Open a key"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_create_key">
		<description>Provide all required information to &lt;b&gt;insert a new key&lt;/b&gt; into a keystore. This key will be used in the current signing process and is stored in the selected keystore.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="tasks/sign_page_create_key.html" label="Create a key"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_create_keystore">
		<description>Provide all required information to &lt;b&gt;create a new keystore&lt;/b&gt; together with &lt;b&gt;a new key&lt;/b&gt;. This key will be used in the current signing process and is stored in the current project folder as [Keystore Name].jks.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="tasks/sign_page_create_keystore.html" label="Create a keystore and key"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_signature_algorithms">
		<description>Select a &lt;b&gt;canonicalization and a transformation algorithm&lt;/b&gt;, a &lt;b&gt;message digest and a signature algorithm&lt;/b&gt;. The &lt;b&gt;signature properties&lt;/b&gt; are optional. A new property can be added by clicking on the + button. The &lt;b&gt;signature id&lt;/b&gt; is optional but makes it much easier to identify the signature. The characters &lt;, &gt;, &amp;, &quot;, &apos; and blanks are not allowed as id (signature id and signature property id), the maximum length is 20 characters. Selecting the &lt;b&gt;Start Encryption Wizard afterwards&lt;/b&gt; checkbox opens the Encryption Wizard after a successful digital signature operation.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="tasks/sign_page_algorithms.html" label="Algorithms and Signature Properties"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_encryption_resource">
		<description>Select the &lt;b&gt;resource&lt;/b&gt; to encrypt (the complete document or a fragment of it), the &lt;b&gt;encryption type&lt;/b&gt; (enveloping or detached) and a &lt;b&gt;key option&lt;/b&gt; (create a new one or use an existing one). The &lt;b&gt;Basic Security Profile&lt;/b&gt; option increases interoperability of Web Service Security.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
		<topic href="tasks/encrypt_page_resource.html" label="Resource and Encryption Type"/>
	</context>
    <context id="wizard_encryption_open_key">
        <description>Provide all required information for the &lt;b&gt;key to use&lt;/b&gt; in the current encryption process.</description>
        <topic href="tasks/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
        <topic href="tasks/encrypt_page_open_key.html" label="Open a key"/>
    </context>
    <context id="wizard_encryption_create_key">
        <description>Provide all required information to &lt;b&gt;insert a new key&lt;/b&gt; into a keystore. This key will be used in the current encryption process and is stored in the selected keystore.</description>
        <topic href="tasks/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
        <topic href="tasks/encrypt_page_create_key.html" label="Create a key"/>
    </context>
    <context id="wizard_encryption_create_keystore">
        <description>Provide all required information to &lt;b&gt;create a new keystore&lt;/b&gt; together with &lt;b&gt;a new key&lt;/b&gt;. This key will be used in the current encryption process and is stored in the current project folder as [Keystore Name].jks.</description>
        <topic href="tasks/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
        <topic href="tasks/encrypt_page_create_keystore.html" label="Create a keystore and key"/>
    </context>
	<context id="wizard_encryption_algorithms">
		<description>Select the &lt;b&gt;encryption algorithms&lt;/b&gt; and decide whether you want to completely encrypt the XML data or keep the root element as plain text. The &lt;b&gt;encryption id&lt;/b&gt; is optional but makes it much easier to identify the encryption. The characters &lt;, &gt;, &amp;, &quot;, &apos; and blanks are not allowed as id, the maximum length is 20 characters. Selecting the Start Digital Signature Wizard afterwards checkbox opens the Digital Signature Wizard after a successful encryption operation.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
		<topic href="tasks/encrypt_page_algorithms.html" label="Algorithms"/>
	</context>
	<context id="xpath_dialog">
		<description>This dialog displays all XML elements in the active XML document as unique XPath expressions. You can select exactly one element you want to use in the current signing or encrypting process.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/sign.html" label="XML Signature Wizard"/>
		<topic href="tasks/encrypt.html" label="XML Encryption Wizard"/>
	</context>
	<context id="wizard_decryption_resource">
		<description>Select the &lt;b&gt;Keystore&lt;/b&gt; used for encrypting this document (-fragment) and enter the &lt;b&gt;password&lt;/b&gt; for the store. Provide the &lt;b&gt;key name&lt;/b&gt; and enter the corresponding &lt;b&gt;password&lt;/b&gt;. If you didn&apos;t enter an &lt;b&gt;encryption id&lt;/b&gt; during the encryption process you can only select to decrypt the first encrypted data found in the selected document. Otherwise select the desired encryption id and click &lt;b&gt;Finish&lt;/b&gt; to start the decryption process.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/decrypt.html" label="XML Decryption Wizard"/>
		<topic href="tasks/decrypt_page_decryption.html" label="Resource and Key information"/>
	</context>
	<context id="preferences_general">
		<description>This preference page allows you to configure the general preferences of the &lt;b&gt;XML Security Tools&lt;/b&gt; including &lt;b&gt;Canonicalization&lt;/b&gt; settings.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/canonicalize.html" label="Canonicalization"/>
		<topic href="setup/preferences.html" label="XML Security Tools Preferences"/>
	</context>
	<context id="preferences_signature">
		<description>This preference page allows you to configure the preferences for the &lt;b&gt;Quick Signature&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Quick Verification&lt;/b&gt; functionality of the &lt;b&gt;XML Security Tools&lt;/b&gt;.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/quickfunctions.html" label="Quick Signature"/>
		<topic href="setup/preferences_sign.html" label="Quick Signature Preferences"/>
	</context>
	<context id="preferences_encryption">
		<description>This preference page allows you to configure the preferences for the &lt;b&gt;Quick Encryption&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Quick Decryption&lt;/b&gt; functionality of the &lt;b&gt;XML Security Tools&lt;/b&gt;.</description>
		<topic href="tasks/quickfunctions.html" label="Quick Encryption"/>
		<topic href="setup/preferences_encrypt.html" label="Quick Encryption Preferences"/>
	</context>
    <context id="signature_view">
        <description>This view displays all &lt;b&gt;XML Signatures&lt;/b&gt; (valid, invalid and unkown) found in the selected XML document. Click &lt;b&gt;Refresh&lt;/b&gt; for a new scan of the active XML document. Select one verification result and click &lt;b&gt;Properties&lt;/b&gt; for detailed information about the selected XML Signature.</description>
        <topic href="tasks/verify.html" label="XML Signatures View"/>
    </context>
</contexts>
